Search

[Home](https://techwiser.com/) » Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

by [Mrinal Saha](https://techwiser.com/author/mrinal/)

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which TechWiser collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://techwiser.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by TechWiser

We collect no personal information and user is free to surf our webpage without any login or registration.

However, we may collect general information like user browser, computer spec etc to improve our service to you.

TechWiser uses cookies so that we can serve you better but if you want you can set your browser to refuse cookies.

All personal data like username email and password is always protected and never is displayed to an unauthorised user.

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

Remember we don’t and will never trade personal information about you.

This site contains product affiliate links from Amazon. We may receive a commission if you make a purchase after clicking on one of these links.

In the future, we may use third-party websites to generate revenue to keep us going but ensure you this will not affect our service and your personal information in any way.

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a Raptive (“Raptive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Raptive will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Raptive’s data usage, click here [https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy](https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy)

Complaints about topics are taken seriously and we look into them immediately.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this site, please contact us at

info: contact@techwiser.com

TechWiser,

C-85, 2nd Floor, Noida Sector 2, NOIDA, 201301

Share [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=https://techwiser.com/privacy-policy/)[Twitter](https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article:%20Privacy%20Policy%20-%20https://techwiser.com/privacy-policy/)[Pinterest](https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftechwiser.com%2Fprivacy-policy%2F&description=Privacy+Policy)[Email](mailto:?subject=Privacy%20Policy&BODY=https://techwiser.com/privacy-policy/)[](#)

© Techwiser Media Private Limited (2012-2024)
